Zeke, why do you have this?
I gave this to Venice.
Can you promise me not to trust anybody?
Except me.
I...
Love him.
And sooner or later,
He will be mine.
So keep that in mind...
Aemie.
Help!
The next time you lay your hands on my wife,
It will surely be the end of your life.
Dong.
Do you want a baby?
I'm her mother.
I came here to spend some time with my daughter.
Apologies, madam.
But Aemie's my wife.
My house,
My rules.
So, how's the business, Roswell?
My wife is putting up her own toy industry.
I'm talking about...
The other business.
How's your relationship with your husband?
Oh.
Well, Mommy, we're married.
I'm the wife,
And he's the hubby.
But most of the time, he's Dodong.
Ayesha.
Huh?
Who are you talking to, Mommy?
Ayesha?
Ayesha.
That's you.
That was supposed to be your name.
I talked to your dad before you were born.
He wanted
Ace if we had a baby boy and
Ayesha if we had a baby girl.
So Daddy Miguel wanted to name me Ayesha?
Not him.
Huh?
What was that, Mommy?
You keep mumbling.
I can't understand you.
What is it?
Are you okay, Mommy?
I'm fine.
Mommy, is it okay if I head up first?
I'm getting sleepy.
I'm going back to Zeke's room.
Okay.
Good night.
Good night, Mommy.
You missed me, didn't you?
Mmm.
Awww, Mommy.
Miss you so much.
Bye-bye, good night.
Good night.
Zeke?
Oh no.
Did he ask me to sleep here because...
There's a ghost?
Am I gonna be the sacrifice?
What if.
Did Moo come back to haunt Zeke because he still can't move on?
So annoying!
Dong!
You scared me!
You're so mean.
I love you, wife.
Let's sleep.
You almost gave me a heart attack.
Dong.
Mm?
Are you mad at me?
Why?
Because...
I didn't say thank you when you said I love you.
Stupid.
You don't say thank you when I say I love you.
You should say,
"I love you too."
Now.
Say it.
It.
Oh!
Dong, this is what I was gonna give you.
What the fuck is this, wife?
Didn't I say I was gonna give you a baby?
Sorry, but he played with baby—
Baby Amiel and Baby Eisz.
Stupid.
You don't have to give me a baby for you to be a perfect wife.
Because for me,
You are more than perfect to be my wife.
Go to sleep, wife.
You're such an idiot.
You're so annoying.
Okay, Dong.
Good night.
I love you.
I love you even more, wife.
Hey.
Okay.
Prepare yourselves.
We'll be having visitors tonight.
Lerwick, Boul.
Your job is to block the roads.
Kill anyone in sight.
I'll be upstairs.
Got it, boss.
Well, guys.
Condolences in advance.
Asshole.
Relax, bro.
Lerwick's just saying his goodbyes.
Everyone already knows you're still injured.
You idiots.
Hurry it up.
Go leave.
Now!
Where's Dong?
Dong?
Hey, where's Dong?
Have you seen him?
Dong?
Hey, Dong?
Dong, where are you?
Huh?
Dodong!
Dong!
Dong?
Where are you, Dong?
Dong.
Dong, Dong.
Hey, Dong.
You're there?
Dong?
Dong!
Dong.
- Baby Ae. - Ah!
Mommy, you scared me.
Have you seen Dong?
Mommy?
He's...
He's downstairs.
Why are you still awake?
I came here to say goodbye.
Huh?
Why goodbye?
Mommy, it's late. There aren't any jeepneys anymore.
I'll tell Lamperouge to drive me home.
I'm just glad you're safe here with your husband.
Okay, Mommy.
Goodnight, Mommy.
Goodnight.
Don't stay up too late. Get some sleep early.
Okay.
But Mommy, get changed before you leave, okay?
Of course.
Oh. It's still early.
It's only 2 AM.
He's so cute when he's sleeping. He looks so innocent.
Wife?
Where are you going?
Well...
I woke up early.
I was gonna make breakfast downstairs.
Wife?
Hey, hey, hey.
It's too early.
I'm so sleepy.
He's so cute.
Hey.
Zeke.
Come on.
We have an early day, right?
We still have training.
There's no training today.
It's April 9.
Huh?
Why?
What's on April 9?
Is it your birthday?
Oh no, I don't have a gift.
Wife, it's exactly two months since the first day we met.
So, no training today.
We're going on a date.
The whole day.
What?!
That's not fair.
I haven't even gotten to hold a gun yet.
I wanna shoot Vash.
End of discussion.
That's not fair, Zeke.
You're so stubborn.
Was it here?
Not there, I'm ticklish!
Hey!
Stop!
Stop it!
I said I'm still sleepy.
Hey!
Stop!
Stop the car!
Stop the car?
Yeah! Stop the car!
Stop it!
Oh, so that's how it is, huh?
- You're messing with me. - Hey!
Hey, not there, Zeke. No.
- Fuck. - Stop fooling around!
Scandal!
Your phone!
- You knock! - I don't have my phone!
Just open it, please.
You do it.
No!
Stay here.
Who the fuck is that?
Who's that?
Bro, bro.
Oh, there's...
So this is one inch—
- The distances are even. - It's sturdy.
- This is hard. - It's one inch.
Didn't know it was this hard.
- So exact. - Solid!
So this is one inch.
Hello guys, good morning.
What the fuck are you guys doing here?
Huh?
- Boul! You got a question? - Boul has a question for you.
- Boul! - Hey, hey!
- Hey! - What is it?
Maybe next time, boss.
Fuck off!
Heh, bye!
Wow!
It's beautiful.
Wow, this is beautiful!
How pretty!
Whoa, no way. She has the same name as Mommy!
Son of a bitch!
Sorry, Mr. Ferrer.
We'll fix this.
Get the vanity table ready.
That's Mr. Ferrer.
Mr. Ferrer?
Mr. Ferrer!
Mr. Roswell.
Fancy meeting you here.
Is this your...
Lovely wife?
Yes.
She's my wife.
Aemie.
Oh!
So this is Caileigh's dad.
I've wanted to meet him for so long.
Caileigh's so lucky. Her dad's still alive.
Mrs. Roswell, why are you looking for me?
Oh, not really.
Why would I be looking for you? You're right here.
I don't have time for this nonsense.
I apologize on my wife's behalf.
Please excuse us.
We have to go already.
What?
Why are his hands so cold?
Is he freezing?
Or is he hot? His palms are sweaty.
I wonder what's wrong with Hubby.
Nice meeting you, Mrs. Roswell.
Oh, just Aemie.
Excuse me, Mr. Ferrer.
Please fill out this form for the delivery details
Of that vanity table.
So you liked this vanity table too?
Are you giving it to Caileigh?
No.
It was...
My wife's.
I've been looking for it ever since she passed away.
Hey, wife.
Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
I just got emotional.
I know how it feels to lose someone you love.
My dad's gone too.
Don't be.
I just wish
I had a daughter like you, Mrs. Roswell.
It's just that my
Biological daughter...
Passed away a long time ago.
Too bad.
You're on the side of the Roswells.
I'll go ahead.
Huh?
Mr. Ferrer sure is confusing.
He said he's been looking for this for so long.
Then,
What did he say?
His biological daughter passed away?
But isn't Cai his daughter?
Wife.
Please don't leave me.
What the fuck was that for?
What are you talking about?
Do I look like I'm leaving?
- Excuse me. - Stupid.
Mr. Ferrer doesn't want the vanity table anymore.
Would you like it?
You done, Dong?
Why did you suddenly want to go to church?
I just wanted to thank Him...
For giving me the best wife.
And I also asked for forgiveness.
And an extension.
What kind of—
What kind of extension?
Hair extensions?
An extension for you and me.
For us.
Huh?
What's Dong talking about?
What does he take us for?
A prepaid promo that needs extending?
You look insane, wife.
I just don't get it.
Don't worry, you don't have to.
Just know
That the next time we'll be here,
It'll be the best wedding for the best wife.
Really, Dong?
Who's getting married?
Slow.
Us, of course.
I'm the slow one?
What?
You're the confusing one, we're already married!
A ceremony.
With all your friends and family.
Oh, oh.
Yeah, that'd be nice.
Then Mommy and cuz will be there.
And your parents too.
Oh.
You still haven't properly introduced me to your parents.
Do I have to?
They're dead.
They won't know a thing.
Right now?
Here?
Why?
They're right here.
They're always with us.
Fine.
Mom, Dad.
This is my life.
Aemie.
Life?
Doesn't that sound wrong? Shouldn't it be "wife"?
What's with Dong?
Ahh.
Mom, Dad, please be patient with Zeke.
He's just like that sometimes.
But don't worry.
I'll teach him some proper manners.
Nice meeting you.
Hey, Dong, want me to introduce you to my dad too?
Well, I already have.
I-I mean,
I'm not yet ready.
I'm sorry, wife.
Not now.
Why not?
I'm scared to lose you.
You must be hungry.
You're talking nonsense again.
Come on.
Yeah, come on. Let's eat.
I'm scared to lose you!
Shh!
Treat me Dong, okay?
Wow!
Good evening, Mrs. Roswell.
Whose birthday is it?
Have a seat, wife.
Wow.
Hey, Dong, let's take a picture.
Come on, let's take one.
Come on, let's take a selfie.
You look stupid, wife.
Look.
I don't look stupid here.
I'm kidding.
You know what you look like?
What?
Damn.
You look like the mother of my future kids.
What?
You already have kids and you never told me?
You all kept it from me?!
Lamperouge.
She didn't get the fucking pick-up line.
- I'm gonna kill your ass. - Oh.
Was that a pick-up line?
Yes, ma'am.
Boss really worked hard memorizing all the lines Lampe taught him.
Anyway.
Shall we, wife?
Oh.
I don't want to.
Going home already?
Idiot.
We're gonna dance.
No, it's just...
Shut up or I'll kiss you.
I love you, wife.
I love you so much too, Dong.
Go forth and multiply!
Whoa!
🎵 The first time that we met, I couldn't believe 🎵
🎵 The beauty that you hold 🎵
🎵 I never thought that I'd be so enchanted 🎵
🎵 I hope this never ends 🎵
🎵 Every night you're here beside me 🎵
🎵 I hope you'll always know 🎵
🎵 All the stars are watching 🎵
🎵 Over both of us 🎵
🎵 Meant to be 🎵
🎵 All the stars are watching 🎵
🎵 Over both of us 🎵
Hello, Ma'am Alyana?
Yaji?
Okay, I'm on my way.
It's nice to finally meet you, Queen.
Don't do that.
There are still things I can't remember from my past.
But I have a hunch.
Roswell already knows everything.
He knows?
Wait.
Queen.
Is Aemie really your daughter?
Yes.
She's my daughter with Eiji.
Making her the legal successor and heiress of Yaji.
Then we must protect her.
We can't guarantee her safety if she's under Roswell's roof.
Especially with how much he hates Yaji.
Roswell loves Aemie.
And my daughter loves him too.
I saw it when I visited them.
But we still don't know if he has other plans.
If Mr. Ferrer finds out—
He can't find out about this.
I don't want to disrupt my daughter's happiness.
Not now.
But.
Mr. Ferrer,
Ordered us to kill Aemie on the day of her toy company's launching.
I already know that.
Who's there?
Ma'am Alyana.
I asked him to be here.
Boulstridge.
I assume you heard what Cassandra just said.
They're planning to kill Ma'am Aemie during the toy company launch?
I want you two to work together to stop that plan.
I don't want Roswell finding out about this, Boulstridge.
If he finds out,
He's going to backfire at Yaji.
I want to end the battle between Yaji and the Roswells.
Even if it's just for Aemie's sake.
If she and Roswell are really in love with each other,
We must end the war between the two biggest mafia groups.
Queen, what if you're wrong?
What if Roswell doesn't love your daughter and she's really just part of—
Boss loves...
Ma'am Aemie.
Ever since he met her, he changed.
He's no longer as heartless as he was before, but he can be ruthless for her.
My only concern is my daughter.
I don't care about Roswell.
I still want to kill him.
Okay, so this is the entire map.
This is where me and Cass are going to be.
Okay?
This is you.
Remember.
So,
I think I'm just missing someone.
Here?
Yeah, here.
- Yup. - Right.
Oh.
Look who decided to show up.
Where have you been?
We're making plans for the launch.
Wasn't the launch supposed to be at Roswell Corporation?
No.
Roswell is gonna change the venue.
And I'm sure of it.
You can't just assume what's in Roswell's mind.
What if he doesn't change it?
So, what are you trying to say, Heather?
What's with you, Cass?
Are you hiding something?
It feels like there's something off with you.
Your attitude's been different lately.
God!
Mei!
I'm just trying to help you create a realistic plan
And you're still doubting me?
You know what?
Let's just get back to actual planning.
Go.
So, this is the area we're gonna do.
Got it.
What's that area?
If you could've been here, you'd know.
Stop.
Stop it.
Hi, Miss Aemie. Can we have lunch today?
I need to tell you something.
Let's just meet at the parking lot near your office
Hi, Kuya Ken, I'm here.
Why aren't you replying? I sent you a one-peso load. Text back pls.
Come on.
Mr. Ken's not here yet.
He said we'd meet here.
And...
Where are we even gonna eat?
Hey!
Aren't you supposed  to be at the office?
You still have a lot to finish.
Where the hell are you?
I'll be right back.
I'm just having lunch with Mr. Ken.
Tell Zeke for me, okay?
And also,
Tell him I love you.
Are you insulting me?
Oh my god!
Did she think I was saying "I love you" to her?
She's so full of herself.
That "I love you" was for Zeke, not you.
Where's Mr. Ken?
Why isn't he here yet?
Why are they wearing masks?
Do they not want to be recognized?
Come with us.
Hey.
So you're awake.
Aren't you scared of us?
Why?
Are you ghosts?
- Where's my daughter? - We need to talk first.
Something happened yesterday.
Yes, I heard.
Yaji.
Impossible.
I know how Yaji operates.
They want to over rule.
If what you're saying is true, Roswell.
Yaji needs a queen to play her role.
They need you.
Aemie!
We've been trying to convince them for years.
They just won't budge.
Why aren't you answering your phone, Aemie?
Maybe Aemie's phone just died, Mr. Roswell.
You know your wife. She never charges it.
I have a bad feeling about this, Lamperouge.
Zeke!